Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 6, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: A Report to the President of the United States, 1963; Publication (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Author: American Foundation on Automation and Employment
  - Item 3: Implications of Automation and Other Technological Developments, 1962; Publication (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: The Williams-Steiger Occupational Safety and Health Act of 1970, Publication (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Box: 6, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Automation: A Challenge to Trade Unions and Industry, 1956; Publication (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Author: ASSET
- Box: 6, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Automation and Its Implication, 1965; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Author: British Productivity Council
  - Item 2: Instructional Material on Productivity and Automation, 1965; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Author: Center for Productivity Motivation
  - Item 3: The Effects of Automation on the Displacement of Personnel, 1964; Publication (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Author: Ellen Miller
    Notes: 25 November 1964
- Box: 6, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: What Workers Should Know About Automation and What Employers Don't Tell Them, 1956; Publication (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Author: Eric Hass and Stephen Emery
  - Item 2: Machines and Working Hours, 1937; Publication (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Author: Machinery and Allied Products Institute
    Notes: October 1937
  - Item 3: Robot Revolution: The Implications of Automation, 1955; Publication (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Author: Socialist Society
- Box: 6, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Automation, 1965; Publication (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Author: Deutschen Angestellten- Gewerkschaft
    Notes: July 1965
- Box: 6, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Automation: The Nut & Bolt Division of Company X, Publication (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Author: Julius Rezler
- Box: 6, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Automation: Nationwide Studies in the United States, 1964; Publication (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Author: Leon Greenburg and Edgar Weinberg
- Box: 6, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: The Automobile Industry: A Case Study of Competition, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Author: General Motors Corporation
    Notes: October 1968
  - Item 2: Automobiles: Basic Industrial Data for Investment Analysis, 1947; Publication (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Author: National Industrial Conference Board, Inc.
  - Item 3: A More Perfect Union: The UAW Public Review Board, Why, What, How, Publication (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Author: The UAW Public Review Board
  - Item 4: Democracy and Public Review: An Analysis of the UAW Public Review Board, 1960; Publication (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Author: Jack Stieber, Walter E. Oberer, Michael Harrington
  - Item 5: Reconversion- Idle Talk Means Idle Men, 1945; Publication (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Author: Automotive Council for War Production
    Notes: September 21, 1944
- Box: 6, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Technological Change & Employment in the Automotive Industry, 1965; Publication (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Notes: September 30, 1965
- Box: 6, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Toward a More Realistic Appraisal of the Automotive Agreement, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Author: Canadian-American Committee
  - Item 2: Canadian Automobile Agreement, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: July 19, 1968
- Box: 6, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Documents on: The Motor Industry, 1965; Publication (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Author: Oxford University Delegacy for Extra-Mural Studies
- Box: 6, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Rapport Betreffende Een Onderzoek Naar De Behoefte Aan Kaderpersoneel In De Motorvoertuigbranche, 1968; Publication (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Author: Stichting Vam
    Language: Dutch.
- Box: 6, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Price Policy and Public Responsibility, 1958; Publication (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Author: Walter P Reuther
    Notes: January 28, 1958
- Box: 6, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Automotive Service Specialist, 1965; Publication (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Box: 6, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The Air Transportation Industry, 1947; Publication (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Author: Stuart G Tipton
  - Item 2: Air Traffic Controllers Retirement, 1970; Publication (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Author: Committee on Post Office and Civil Service
    Notes: November 21, 1969
- Box: 7, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Wages, Working Conditions and Social Security Benefits in the Baking Industry in Selected Countries: A Comparative Study, 1963; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Author: International Union of Food and Allied Workers' Associations
- Box: 7, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Baking Industry, 1946; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Author: Mary Kinnavey Moore
- Box: 7, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Guide to the Balance of Payments, 1966; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Author: Tom Drinkwater
  - Item 2: The International Position of the Dollar, 1961; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Author: Committee for Economic Development
    Notes: May 1961
  - Item 3: The United States Balance of Payments Position, 1963; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: The Rescue of the Dollar, 1963; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Author: Wilson E Schmidt
  - Item 5: The U.S. Balance of Payments and International Monetary Reserves, 1966; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Author: Howard S Piquet
    Notes: February 1966
  - Item 6: Joint Economic Committee, 1962; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Author: Joint Economic Committee
  - Item 7: The Balance of Payments Statistics of the United States, 1965; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: The United States Balance of Payments, 1964; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Discriminatory Ocean Freight Rates and the Balance of Payments, 1965; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Notes: June 30, 1965
- Box: 7, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Story of American Banking, 1963; Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Author: The American Bankers Association
  - Item 2: A Working Program: Clerical Cost and Work Measurement at the National Bank of Detroit, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Box: 7, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Survey of the Barbering Industry in Ontario, 1968; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Author: Ontario Department of Labour
    Notes: August 1968
- Box: 7, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Australian Natives' Association: Its Aims and Influence on the Australian Scene, 1963; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Author: Bryan J. Kelleher
- Box: 7, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Life Story of a Forgotten Giant - Peter J. McGuire, 1946; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Author: A. Charles Corotis and Chales W. Phillips
- Box: 7, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Testimony of Mr. William J. Strong, 1899; Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Author: Subcommission on Transportation
    Notes: November 22, 1899
- Box: 7, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Handbook of Representative Industrial Jobs for Blind Workers, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Author: Federal Security Agency
  - Item 2: Adjustment and Prevocational Training for the Blind, 1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Notes: March 1949
  - Item 3: Causes of Blindness Among Recipients of Aid to the Blind, 1947; Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Author: Ralph G Hurlin, Sadie Saffian, Carl E Rice
  - Item 4: The Activities of Federal-State and Private Agencies Concerned with Work for the Blind and Preventing Blindness, 1940; Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Notes: October 1940
- Box: 7, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Act to Consolidate the Laws Relating to the Payment of Pensions to Blind Persons and of Grants-in-Aid for the Promotion of the Promotion of the Welfare of Such Persons and Matters Incidental Thereto, 1962; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Author: Republic of South Africa
    Language: English; Dutch.
- Box: 7, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Blind Person Can Do the Job, 1972; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Author: The American Association of Workers for the Blind
    Notes: September 1972
  - Item 2: The Story of the Wagner-O'Day Act, 1966; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Author: Robert LeFevre
  - Item 3: Piano Industry Conference, 1961; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Author: Department of Health, Education and Welfare
    Notes: April 13,14,15, 1961
- Box: 7, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Hold the Fort!, 1971; Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Author: Paul Scheips
- Box: 7, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Tutto Sulla Gratifica Natalizia e 13 Mensilita, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Author: Adone Ferrara
    Language: Italian.
- Box: 7, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Building Trades Strikes Against Open Shop Products are Unlawful, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Author: League for Industrial Rights
  - Item 2: More About Boycotts in Electrical Industry, 1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Author: National Electrical Manuracturers Association
    Notes: August 17, 1949
  - Item 3: Manual for Action in Support of the G.E. Strikers, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Author: Citizens' Committee to Support the G.E. Strikers
- Box: 7, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Manufacturing Industries, 1945-46. No. 26. Breweries, 1946; Publication (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Author: Commonwealth Bureau of Census and Statistics, Canberra
- Box: 7, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Family Budget, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Recommendations Concerning Family Budget Enquiries in Europe, 1966; Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Personal Money Management, 1962; Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Author: American Bankers' Association
  - Item 4: Standard Budgets for Elderly Persons: Problems of Concept, Methods and Interpretation, Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Author: Helen H Lamale, Ewan Clague
  - Item 5: A Family Budget Standard, 1963; Publication (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Author: Community Council of Greater New York
- Box: 7, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Budgeting for National Objectives, 1966; Publication (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Notes: January 1966
- Box: 7, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: An Economic Profile of the Buffalo Metropolitan Area, 1962; Publication (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Author: Eric Polisar
    Notes: November 1962
- Box: 7, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Act of 1st March 1946 Respecting The National Housing Bank Of Norway, Publication (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Author: Norway
  - Item 2: Act of 19 July, 1946 Respecting Expropriation and Prohibition Against Building Concerning Ground Areas, Publication (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Box: 7, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Resolution of Jurisdictional Disputes in the Building Trades and Economic Prospects for the Industry, 1957; Publication (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Author: University of Michigan
    Notes: June 28, 1957
  - Item 2: Basis of Effective Labor Relations in Building Industry, 1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Author: Building Trades Employers' Association
  - Item 3: A Segment of Construction Activity in the 1947 Interindustry Relations Study, 1953; Publication (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Occupational Outlook Information: Long-Range Employment Prospects by State and Region, 1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 20)
    Author: Veterans' Administration
    Notes: May 1949
- Box: 7, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Planning, 1943; Publication (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Notes: September 28, 1943
  - Item 2: British Measures for Securing Housing and Building Labor, 1944-45, 1945; Publication (Box 7, Folder 21)
    Author: Bureau of Labor Statistics
- Box: 7, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Interdependence and Uncertainty: A Study of the Building Industry, 1966; Publication (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Author: Tavistock Institute
- Box: 7, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Care and Feeding of Bulletin Boards, 1948; Publication (Box 7, Folder 23)
    Author: The Borden Company
- Box: 7, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Key Business Ratios, 1964; Publication (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Author: Dun V Bradstreet, Inc.
- Box: 7, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: American Business Activity Since 1790, 1946; Publication (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Author: The Cleveland Trust Company
  - Item 2: Business Booms and Depressions: The 1947 Edition, Publication (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Author: The Century Press, Inc.
    Notes: Special Study of: How Much is One Billion Dollars?
  - Item 3: Must We Have Boom and Bust?, 1946; Publication (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Author: The American Economic Foundation
    Notes: Sunday, September 22, 1946
  - Item 4: The Federal Reserve and the Business Cycle, 1961; Publication (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Author: Colin D. Campbell
  - Item 5: Management Action to Promote Business Stability, 1961; Publication (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Why We Have Depressions and Recessions, 1962; Publication (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Author: Alfred Baker Lewis
- Box: 7, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Education for Business, 1947; Publication (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Author: Sheldon R. Coons
  - Item 2: Business Experience for Business Teachers, 1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Author: B. Frank Kyker
  - Item 3: The Challenge of Business Education, 1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Author: University of Chicago
  - Item 4: The Collegiate Curriculum in Business, 1948; Publication (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Author: Alpha Kappa Psi Fraternity
- Box: 7, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Directory of Private Business Schools in the United States, 1948; Publication (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Author: National Council of Business Schools
- Box: 7, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Management Studies in Technical Colleges, 1965; Publication (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Author: United Kingdom Department of Education and Science
- Box: 7, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Postgraduate Education for Business, 1961; Publication (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Author: M.E. Beesley
  - Item 2: Educating Tomorrow's Managers, 1964; Publication (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Author: The Committee for Economic Development
    Notes: October 1964
- Box: 7, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Big Progress and Big Business Go Together, 1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Author: Charles E. Wilson
    Notes: November 30, 1949
- Box: 7, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: A Statement on Business Ethics and a Call for Action, 1962; Publication (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Box: 7, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Businessmen in Fiction; The Capitalist and Executive in American Novels, 1955; Publication (Box 7, Folder 32)
    Author: Robert A. Kavesh
    Notes: September 1955
- Box: 7, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: The Businessman in the Novel, 1959; Publication (Box 7, Folder 33)
    Author: Charlotte Georgi
- Box: 7, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Your Business in the Next 15 Years, 1964; Publication (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Author: Research Institute of America, Inc.
    Notes: June 30, 1964
  - Item 2: The Coming Economic Crisis in America, 1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Author: Earl Browder
    Notes: February 14, 1949
  - Item 3: Perspective for Business Expansion: A Memorandum to Kalamazoo Businessmen, 1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Author: Julius T. Wendzel
    Notes: August 1949
  - Item 4: What's Ahead for Business and Industry in 1947, Publication (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Item 5: Short-Range Business Forecasting, 1962; Publication (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Author: Philip B. Hartley
  - Item 6: Business Cycle Indicators for States and Regions, 1961; Publication (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Author: Gerhard Bry
    Notes: July 1961
- Box: 7, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Fundamentals of Forms Management, Publication (Box 7, Folder 35)
    Author: S.A. Fernald
- Box: 7, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Wages Procedures, 1949; Publication (Box 7, Folder 36)
    Author: A. Abbott
    Notes: October 12, 1949
- Box: 7, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Rate of Failure & Average Liability Per Failure in Manufacturing, 1946 vs. 1940, By Line, 1947; Publication (Box 7, Folder 37)
    Author: Dun & Bradstreet, Inc.
  - Item 2: Commercial Failures in the United States, 1857-1945 Inclusive, 1946; Publication (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Item 3: Why Do Businesses Fail?, 1951; Publication (Box 7, Folder 37)
    Author: Griffith M. Jones
    Notes: March 1951
  - Item 4: Commercial Failures in the United States, 1857 to Date, 1948; Publication (Box 7, Folder 37)
    Notes: 1857-1948
  - Item 5: The Milton Plan: An Exercise in Manpower Planning and the Transfer of Production, Publication (Box 7, Folder 37)
    Author: Alan Fox
- Box: 7, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: What Happens When Company Employees Get Into Politics, 1960; Publication (Box 7, Folder 38)
    Author: The Public Opinion Index for Industry
    Notes: July 1960, Small Copy
  - Item 2: What Happens When Company Employees Get Into Politics, 1960; Publication (Box 7, Folder 38)
    Notes: July 1960, Large Copy
  - Item 3: BIPAC to Cope With COPE, Publication (Box 7, Folder 38)
    Author: John Angle
  - Item 4: Company Participation in the Political Process, 1961; Publication (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Item 5: Action Course Volunteer Program, 1963; Publication (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Item 6: Employer Policies on Political Activity, 1973; Publication (Box 7, Folder 38)
    Notes: May 1973
- Box: 7, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: A Handbook for Forms Design and Analysis, 1964; Publication (Box 7, Folder 39)
    Author: Management Planning Department of General Services
  - Item 2: A Guide to Installing Forms Management, 1964; Publication (Box 7, Folder 39)
    Notes: June 1964
  - Item 3: A Program for Forms Management, 1964; Publication (Box 7, Folder 39)
    Notes: January 1964
- Box: 7, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Report of the Assembly Interim Committee on Civil Service and State Personnel: House Resolution No. 361, 1961, 1962; Publication (Box 7, Folder 40)
    Author: Assembly of the State of California
    Notes: December 1962
- Box: 7, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Special Service to Veterans, Publication (Box 7, Folder 41)
    Author: California State Employment Service
- Box: 7, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Vote CIO and Get a Soviet America, 1944; Publication (Box 7, Folder 42)
    Author: Joseph P. Kamp
- Box: 7, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: 5000 Facts About Canada, 1946; Publication (Box 7, Folder 43)
    Author: Ontario Publishing Co.
    Notes: 1946 Annual Edition
- Box: 7, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: National Accounts: Income and Expenditure 1938-1945, 1946; Publication (Box 7, Folder 44)
    Author: Canada Department of Trade and Commerce
- Box: 7, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Brief to Special Senate Committee on Poverty, 1970; Publication (Box 7, Folder 45)
    Author: The New Brunswick Federation of Labor
    Notes: August 1970
  - Item 2: Reconstruction, Social Security and Health Insurance, 1943; Publication (Box 7, Folder 45)
    Author: Ian A. Mackenzie
- Box: 8, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: White Paper on Immigration, 1967; Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Author: Jean Marchand
- Box: 8, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: U.S.-Canadian Free Trade: The Potential Impact on the Canadian Economy, 1968; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Author: Paul Wonnacott and Ronald J. Wonnacott
- Box: 8, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Le Service Consultatif de la Main-d'oeuvre, 1970; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Author: Ministere de la Main-d'oeuvre et de L'Immigration
- Box: 8, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Some Elements of Newness in a Basic Programme of Statistics, 1965; Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Author: The Canadian Statistical Review
    Notes: August 1965
- Box: 8, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Employment and Housing Problems of Migratory Workers in New York and New Jersey Canning Industries, 1943, 1944; Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Box: 8, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report of Seasonal Food Processing Activities, 1946; Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Notes: November 16-30, 1946, December 5, 1946
  - Item 2: Child Labor and Hours in New York State Canneries, Summer 1944, 1945; Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Author: New York State Division of Wages, Hours, Women and Child Labor
    Notes: June 1945
- Box: 8, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Vegetable, Fruit and Fruit Juice Canning Industry in Puerto Rico, 1947; Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Notes: June 1947
- Box: 8, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Capital Goods and American Progress, 1937; Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Notes: June 1937
- Box: 8, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Modern-Day Capitalism: Progress, Problems, Potential, 1966; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: We Need a Fifth Freedom, 1949; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Author: Herman W. Steinkraus
    Notes: September 1949
  - Item 3: Competitive Enterprise Versus Planned Economy, 1945; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Author: H.W. Prentis
    Notes: August 1945
  - Item 4: People and Profits, 1948; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Author: Byron G. Moon Company, Inc.
  - Item 5: Private Enterprise in the Development of the Americas, 1946; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Author: U.S. Department of State
  - Item 6: Capitalism Yesterday & Today, 1962; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Author: Maurice Dobb
  - Item 7: Why Kill the Goose?, 1947; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Author: Sherman Rogers
  - Item 8: The Public Responsibilities of Big Companies, 1948; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Author: Eugene Holman
    Notes: November 8, 1948
  - Item 9: Fallacies About Our Private Enterprise System, 1944; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Notes: March 1944
  - Item 10: The Threat to Independent Business, 1946; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Author: Wendell Berge
    Notes: December 11, 1946
  - Item 11: Business in a Democracy, 1943; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Author: National Industrial Information Committee
    Notes: December 1943
  - Item 12: Fallacies About Our Private Enterprise System, 1941; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Notes: January 1941
  - Item 13: Free Enterprise- How Long Can it Survive?, 1949; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Author: Leonard W. Trester
    Notes: January 11, 1949
  - Item 14: The Delivered Price, Generally, 1947; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Notes: January 31, 1947